{
    "Changes": [
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Shane"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "What's your most favorite stuff?",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Shane loved false none}}}}", // get gift taste for Shane, loved gift taste, not Shane's relative, not excluding any item
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Shane loved true none}}}}",// get gift taste for one of Shane's relative, loved gift taste, yes Shane's relative, not excluding any item
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Alex"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "What's your most favorite stuff?",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Alex loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Alex loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Sebastian"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "What's your most favorite stuff?",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Sebastian loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Sebastian loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Sam"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "What's your most favorite stuff?",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Sam loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Sam loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Elliott"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "What's your most favorite stuff?",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Elliott loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: Leah, Willy}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Elliott 1 2 1"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Harvey"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "What's your most favorite stuff?",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Harvey loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Maru loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
                // Harvey doesn't have relative
                // "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                //     "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                //     "Weight": 10,
                //     "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                //     "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Harvey loved true none}}}}",
                //     "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                // }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Penny"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "What's your most favorite stuff?",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Penny loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Penny loved true 303-346-348-459-873}}}}", // get gift taste for one of Penny's relative, loved gift taste, yes Penny's relative, but do not suggest item id that have one in these ids: 303-346-348-459-873
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Penny 1 2 1"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: Sam, Vincent, Jas}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Penny 1 2 2"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Haley"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "What's your most favorite stuff?",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Haley loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Haley loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Haley 1 2 1"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: Alex, Alex}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Haley 1 2 2"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Emily"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "What's your most favorite stuff?",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Emily loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Emily loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Emily 1 2 1"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: Gus, Shane}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Emily 1 2 2"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Maru"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "What's your most favorite stuff?",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Maru loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Maru loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Maru 1 2 1"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random: Harvey, Penny}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Maru 1 2 2"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Abigail"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "What's your most favorite stuff?",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Abigail loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Abigail loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Leah"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "What's your most favorite stuff?",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Leah loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Elliott loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                }
                // "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                //     "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                //     "Weight": 10,
                //     "QuestionText": "Ask for gift suggestion",
                //     "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,2}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Leah loved true none}}}}",
                //     "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                // }
            }
        }
    ]
}